<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://priyagole.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://priyagole.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2023-01-05T21:43:18+05:30</updated><id>https://priyagole.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blank</title><subtitle>My personal website. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Hello World!</title><link href="https://priyagole.github.io/welcome/2022/12/25/giscus-comments.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hello World!"/><published>2022-12-25T21:29:00+05:30</published><updated>2022-12-25T21:29:00+05:30</updated><id>https://priyagole.github.io/welcome/2022/12/25/giscus-comments</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://priyagole.github.io/welcome/2022/12/25/giscus-comments.html"><![CDATA[<p>Hello Guys!<br/> I am Priya. You are here most likely because you already know who I am. The about page has all my academic interests and details. So, in this post, I will introduce you to the “non-academic” me :)</p> <blockquote> <h6 id="we-all-seem-to-be-getting-more-self-obsessed-by-the-day-turn-on-your-tv-or-open-a-web-browser-and-narcissism-hits-you-smack-in-the-face--everything-screams-me-me-me">We all seem to be getting more self-obsessed by the day. Turn on your TV or open a web browser, and narcissism hits you smack in the face — everything screams ME! ME! ME!</h6> <h6 id="-source">~ <a href="http://www.mindbodygreen.com/0-17248/how-to-teach-your-kids-to-be-compassionate.html">source</a></h6> </blockquote> <p>So, apart from being a nerd, I love interacting with people. I am a sucker for good conversations. I like meeting new people, talking to them, and getting to know them a bit better. Yes, I am an extreme extrovert, always high on energy. So, if you want to get in touch, feel free to ping me. If you are from IITK, it’s always a good idea to meet up and chat over a cup of chai (or coffee?).</p> <p>I am not “sporty,” but I like playing badminton occasionally. I am quite into music (I mean, everyone is). I don’t have any particular preference; it is mood-dependent, usually just a mix of pop, hip-hop, and rap. I also like playing instruments. I learned the keyboard and flute during school and wish to continue learning, but I don’t find time to.</p> <blockquote> <h6 id="there-is-no-such-thing-as-i-do-not-have-the-time-this-is-all-just-a-matter-of-priorities">There is no such thing as ‘I do not have the time’. This is all just a matter of priorities.</h6> <h6 id="-maciej-aniserowicz">~ Maciej Aniserowicz</h6> </blockquote> <p>I spend my time sleeping, binging YouTube (kudos to the YT recommendation algorithm), or watching anime. I am open to all sorts of recommendations (except for horror).</p> <p>If you are still reading, kudos to you. It takes effort to go through all the unnecessary information about some random individual. Feel free to contact me via email or social media if you want to chat.<br/> And have a great day ahead :)<br/> Sayonara!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="Welcome"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[An introduction to me and my blog.]]></summary></entry></feed>